<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pokemon Academy</string>
    <string name="planning_content">
        <![CDATA[
        <h5> <font color=\"#ffbf00\">Requirements:</h5>"
                "<p>They are specifications of what should be implemented, "
                "descriptions of how a system should behave, or of a system property/attribute.</p>"
                  "<h5> <font color=\"#ffbf00\"> Requirement Engineering</h5><p>It is about identifying "
                "the purpose of a software system and the contexts in which it will be used. "  
                "It refers to the activity of requirement development, which includes elicitation, "  
                "specification, analysis and management of stakeholder requirements.</p>"
                  "<br>There are two Requirement Elicitation techniques:<br></br></br>"
                  "<br><b>Technique 1:</b><br></br></br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Examine Documents: reuse existing or related documents, read standards or government regulations.\n</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Interview stakeholders: conduct focus groups with customers to gather idea and needs.\n</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Use questionnaires or marketing surveys for quantitative data.<br></br></br>"
                  "<br><b>Technique 2:</b><br></br></br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Watch users do their job.</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Prototyping: create interface to help customers better understand the system.\n</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Task analysis: make use cases/ scenarios.<br></br></br>"
                  "<h5> <font color=\"#ffbf00\"> Requirement Analysis</h5>"
                  "<p>Decompose high-level requirements into details and identify priorities."
                  "<br><b>Requirement Specification Approaches:</b><br></br></br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; <b>Textual:</b> vision and scope document, use case document, SRS.</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; <b>Graphical:</b> structured analysis models (data flow diagram, entity-relationship diagram, dialog map), OO analysis models.</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; <b>Formal:</b> formal specification languages.</br>"
                  "<p><b>Software Requirement Specification</b> is a set of precisely-stated properties and constraints "
                "that a software system must satisfy, and a complete description of the external "  
                "behaviour of a system. The objectives of SRS are to achieve agreement regarding the "  
                "requirements among developers, customers and other stakeholders, as well as provide basis for design and system testing.</p>
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_mini_quiz_landing_page">Mini Quiz</string>
    <string name="analysis_content">
        <![CDATA[
            "<p>In the analysis phase, end user business requirements are analysed and project goals "
                "are converted into defined system functions. The three primary activities involved in the analysis "
                "phase are as follows: </p>"
                "<br>&#8226; Gathering business requirements\n</br>"
                "<br>&#8226; Creating process diagrams\n</br>"
                "<br>&#8226; Performing detailed analysis<br></br></br>"
                "<p><b>Business requirement gathering<b> is the most crucial part of this level of SDLC."
                " Business requirements are a brief set of business functionalities that the system needs"
                " to meet in order to be successful.</p>"
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="design_content">
        <![CDATA[
            "<p>In the design phase, the desired features and operations of the system are described. "
                "The system design provides overall guidance on system functions, performance requirements,"
                " security requirements, platform characteristics and should comprise:</p>"
                "<br>&#8226; Business rules/application logic\n</br>"
                "<br>&#8226; Interface design (app-tp-app, app-to-db)\n</br>"
                "<br>&#8226; User Interfaces (GUI)\n</br>"
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="implementation_content">
        <![CDATA[
            "<p>During implementation, all the documents from the previous phase are transformed into the actual system. "
                "It is when the coding phase begins, where the design specified in the design
                document into executable programming language code. The output of the coding phase
                is the source code for the software.</p>"
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="testing_content">
        <![CDATA[
            "<p>Integration and testing includes detection of errors in the software. The testing process
            starts with a test plan that recognises test-related activities, such as test case generation, testing
            criteria, and resource allocation for testing.</p>"
            "<p>The code is tested and mapped against the design document created in the design phase.
             The output of the testing phase is a test report containing error that occurred while testing
              the application.</p>"
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="maintenance_content">
        <![CDATA[
            "<p>In the maintenance phase, any necessary enhancements, corrections and changes will be made
             to make sure that the system continues to work, and stay updated to meet the business goals.</p>"
            "<p>It is necessary to maintain and upgrade the system from time to time, so it can adapt
             to future needs. The three primary activities involved in the maintenance phase are as follows:</p>"
             "<br>&#8226; Support the system users\n</br>"
             "<br>&#8226; System maintenance\n</br>"
             "<br>&#8226; System changes and adjustment\n</br>"
         ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
