<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pokemon Academy</string>
    <string name="planning_content">
        <![CDATA[
        <h5> <font color=\"#784C27\">Requirements:</h5>"
                "<p>They are specifications of what should be implemented, "
                "descriptions of how a system should behave, or of a system property/attribute.</p>"
                  "<h5> <font color=\"#784C27\"> Requirement Engineering</h5><p>It is about identifying "  
                "the purpose of a software system and the contexts in which it will be used. "  
                "It refers to the activity of requirement development, which includes elicitation, "  
                "specification, analysis and management of stakeholder requirements.</p>"
                  "<br>There are two Requirement Elicitation techniques:<br></br></br>"
                  "<br><b>Technique 1:</b><br></br></br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Examine Documents: reuse existing or related documents, read standards or government regulations.\n</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Interview stakeholders: conduct focus groups with customers to gather idea and needs.\n</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Use questionnaires or marketing surveys for quantitative data.<br></br></br>"
                  "<br><b>Technique 2:</b><br></br></br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Watch users do their job.</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Prototyping: create interface to help customers better understand the system.\n</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; Task analysis: make use cases/ scenarios.<br></br></br>"
                  "<h5> <font color=\"#784C27\"> Requirement Analysis</h5>"
                  "<p>Decompose high-level requirements into details and identify priorities."
                  "<br><b>Requirement Specification Approaches:</b><br></br></br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; <b>Textual:</b> vision and scope document, use case document, SRS.</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; <b>Graphical:</b> structured analysis models (data flow diagram, entity-relationship diagram, dialog map), OO analysis models.</br>"
                  "<br>&#8226; <b>Formal:</b> formal specification languages.</br>"
                  "<p><b>Software Requirement Specification</b> is a set of precisely-stated properties and constraints "
                "that a software system must satisfy, and a complete description of the external "  
                "behaviour of a system. The objectives of SRS are to achieve agreement regarding the "  
                "requirements among developers, customers and other stakeholders, as well as provide basis for design and system testing.</p>
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_mini_quiz_landing_page">MiniQuizLandingPage</string>
</resources>
